cylive.com 2008-12-19

# Cylive Privacy Policy

## March 1st, 2006 

### Personal Information

Cylive collects some personal information, including email addresses, when individuals register to use the Cylive website and services, post a link to the Cylive website or submit questions, comments or bug reports. We may also, at times, collect our users' IP addresses and information regarding our users' use of our website and services. We may use such IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, track movement within our website and, if necessary, deny service in accordance with our Terms of Use . We may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times and browser type. Unless required by law, we will not share our users' personal information, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and usage information, except in aggregate or anonymous form, with third parties. 

In order to offer and provide optimized and personalized services, we use cookies to store and sometimes track information about our users. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's computer hard drive.

### Uses

Cylive stores and maintains your account information and the content that you create on various database in order to provide the service. The content of data may be fed to computer algorithms to better target the advertising content. 

### Your choices

You can change your account and profile settings to not publish your information on publicly accessible areas of the website. You have the ability to modify and remove content that you create. Once you modify or remove your content, residual copies of such content may reside for an indefinite time on backup storage.

Our services give you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. We will never automatically send you information/offers you do not want. You must choose to receive them.

If your account is reported to be abusing the services in a manner that is inconsistent with the law, we will take any appropriate measures to protect other users of the service upon validation of such claims. Such violations, along with your information could also be reported to authorities.

### More information 

Cylive reserves the right to modify all or some of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on our website so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorization from the appropriate user(s) to do otherwise.

If Cylive becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website or your dealings with Cylive, you can send an e-mail, in English, to [privacy@cylive.com](mailto:privacy@cylive.com).
